Augusto Kerber

Florianópolis, SC, Brazil

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/augusto-kerber-10a564169/

Demoreel: https://vimeo.com/499251259

Tel.: (+55)47 99999-0026 E-mail address: augusto-kerber@hotmail.com

3D Animator

Passionate and creative animator, with over two years of experience, who excels working on fast paced environments, always seeking to achieve a high quality animation. Proficient with Maya, 3DS Max, Photoshop, After Effects, Illustrator and Zbrush. Experience working with multiple animation styles and media such as 2D and 3D animated games, television shows, educational content and advertising.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Plot Kids - Brazil Apr 2019 - Jan 2020 3D Animator

- Animate 3D Characters and Environment
 - Create and compose 3D scenes on Unity
 - Deliver a final product to be used on a Virtual Reality system
 - Work with a team to ensure the best quality product is being delivered

Design Lab UFSC - Brazil

3D Animator July 2018 - Dec 2018

- MOCAP animation clean-up and refinement
- Organize scenes on Autodesk MotionBuilder
- Produce and capture motion capture studio shots

Up!, Bubu and the little Owls - Brazil

Executive-production Assistant Internship

- Auxiliate the production of an animated TV Series
- Organize and synchronize time scripts
- Motion Design Animation

DV3 Productions, Brazil

Video Editor Jan 2016 - Feb 2017

July 2017 - Oct 2017

- Edit educational and business videos with the Adobe Package
- Deliver high quality products on short turnarounds

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Animation Jan 2016 - Dec 2019

Federal University of Santa Catarina